Assembly of Governmental Employees Records 5769
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Publications. (Box 19)
  - Out of Binder 1, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Out of Binder 2, 1967-1970 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Out of Binder 2, 1971-1979 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Out of Binder 2, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Out of Binder 3, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Out of Binder 3, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Out of Binder 3, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Out of Binder 3, 1971-1975 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Out of Binder 4, 1973-1980 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Out of Binder 4, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Out of Binder 4, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Out of Binder 5, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Out of Binder 5, 1979-1980 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Out of Binder 5, 1977-1980 (Box 19, Folder 16)
- #10 Ex Dir. Leg Conf. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  Cassette Tape
- Business Products Cassette Tape (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Business Products Cassette Tape (Box 20, Folder 3)
- '#2' (Box 20, Folder 4)
- '#3' (Box 20, Folder 5)
- #4 Denver (Box 20, Folder 6)
- #8 Denver (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Ampex Cassette Tape (Box 20, Folder 8)
- 1978 Wov Leadership conference (Box 20, Folder 9)
- #3 Leg. Conf. 12/14/79, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Bargaining Without Statutory Authority 5:00pm - 5:20pm (Box 20, Folder 11)
- Preparing your Assoc. for Bargaining 10:45am - 11:15am (Box 20, Folder 12)
- #4 Start of Pension Panel Leg. Conf. 12/14/79, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 13)
- 1983 General Assembly Tape #1 8:40am - 9:35am (Box 20, Folder 14)
- 08-18-83 Board Meeting (Md) #1, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 15)
- 1978 Leadership Conf. (Box 20, Folder 16)
- Leg. Conf. 12/14/79, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 17)
- #4 Leg. Conf. 12/14/79, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 18)
- Lanier Business Products Cassette Tape (Box 20, Folder 19)
- Leg. Conf. 12/14/79, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 20)
- Lanier Business Products Cassette Tape (Box 20, Folder 21)
- #5-29th GA (Box 20, Folder 22)
- BASF Performance Series Cassette Tape (Box 20, Folder 23)
- Scotch Highlander Cassette Tape (Box 20, Folder 24)
- #4 (Box 20, Folder 25)
- Lanier Business Products (Box 20, Folder 26)
- #2 Leg cong. 12/14/79, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 27)
- #1 Leg. Conf. 12/14/79, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  Cassette Tapes
- James Marshall 1977 General Assembly (Unit elections) (Box 20, Folder 29)
- Denver #3 (Box 20, Folder 30)
- #3 Leg. Conf. 12/14/79, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 31)
- #5 Leg. Conf. 12/14/79 Pension Panel "A Look at Age", 1979 (Box 20, Folder 32)
- #1 Denver (Box 20, Folder 33)
- #2 Denver (Box 20, Folder 34)
- #5 Denver (Box 20, Folder 35)
- Lanier Business Products (Box 20, Folder 36)
- Tape #2 General Assembly (Box 20, Folder 37)
- Bargaining Without Statutory Authority 3:30pm - 4:00pm (Box 20, Folder 38)
- Nov. 1978 Leadership Conf. (Box 20, Folder 39)
- How to Counter Union Propoganda 2:45-3:15pm (Box 20, Folder 40)
- #7 Denver (Box 20, Folder 41)
- 8/18/83 Board Meeting 2nd Tape (Box 20, Folder 42)
- #8 Leg conf. 12/14/79, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 43)
- #7 Leg. Conf. 12/14/79, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 44)
- #6 Leg. Conf. 12/15/79, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 45)
- #3 (Lanier C. Tape) (Box 20, Folder 46)
- #1 (Lanier C. Tape) (Box 20, Folder 47)
- (Unlabeled Cassette Tape) (Box 20, Folder 48)
- #2 (Lanier C. Tape) (Box 20, Folder 49)
- #1 Denver Board (Box 20, Folder 50)
- #3 Denver Board (Box 20, Folder 51)
- (Unlabeled C. Tape) (Box 20, Folder 52)
- Bd. Mtg. Tape 1 3/19/83 (Box 20, Folder 53)
- (Unlabeled Cassette Tape) (Box 20, Folder 54)
- Bd. Mtg. 2nd Tape 3/19/83 (Box 20, Folder 55)
- Part 3 (Box 20, Folder 56)
- Bd. Mtg Tape 3 3/17/83, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 57)
- Part 2 (Box 20, Folder 58)
- #1 Bs. 8/23/81, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 59)
- #2 Bd. 8/23/81, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 60)
- Public Employees Investment Corporation, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 61)
- Davenport Dillard Inc., 1973 (Box 20, Folder 62)
- Davenport Dillard Incorporated, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 63)
- Deferred Comp. - Memo, Correspondence (AGE), 1974 (Box 20, Folder 64)
- Misc., 1974-1976 (Box 20, Folder 65)